Guide to the ROADwomen Records
University of Houston Libraries
ROADwomen Records
1994-2008
1997-2002
02/2011-014
River Oaks Area Democratic Women
14.00 linear feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
The collection is primarily concerned with the River Oaks Area Democratic Women, though it also contains material for both Democrat and Republican political candidates. Material in the collection includes correspondence, business and financial records, photographs, and the organization’s publication, Register. The collection is divided into six series: Governance, ROADwomen Register, Events and Programs, Organizations, Campaign Materials, and Various Materials. All series are arranged topically and chronologically except for Organizations and Campaign Material, which are organized alphabetically by name group or candidate.
Historical Note:
Incorporated in March 1997, the River Oaks Area Democratic Women's (ROADwomen) main goal was to fill a void in Democratic activity within the city of Houston, Texas. Organizations for Democratic women that had operated in the city prior to 1997 had fallen into inactivity leaving no representation for these politically activity women, as opposed to the twenty-five groups that existed for Republican women in Harris County. ROADwomen became a “home for the politically disengaged upwardly mobile Democratic woman” in the area. The goals for the ROADwomen were, and continue to be efforts to elect Democrats to office, with a special emphasis on electing pro-choice Democratic women; to influence the Democratic Party to continue its historic role as a party that promotes social justice and equal rights for all people; and act as an organization that educates Houstonians about important political issues affecting them.
The founding members consisted of Dalia Stokes, Elizabeth Guffy, Sherry Merfish, Muffie Moroney, Judy Reiner, and Kay Staley. Since 1997, the organization has worked with like-minded groups to support and elect quality Democratic candidates at all levels of government.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
Democratic Party (Tex.); River Oaks Area Democratic Women
Genre/Form of Material:
Administrative records; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Newsletters; Photographs
Geographic Name:
River Oaks (Tex.)
Topical Term:
Political campaigns -- Texas -- Houston; Politicians; Women -- Political activity -- Texas -- Houston; Women -- Societies and clubs -- Texas -- Houston
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Related Materials:
Annise Parker Papers (http://archon.lib.uh.edu/index.php?p=collections/controlcard&id=397)
Scope and Contents
The collection is primarily concerned with the River Oaks Area Democratic Women, though it also contains material for both Democrat and Republican political candidates. Material in the collection includes correspondence, business and financial records, photographs, and the organization’s publication, Register. The collection is divided into six series: Governance, ROADwomen Register, Events and Programs, Organizations, Campaign Materials, and Various Materials. All series are arranged topically and chronologically except for Organizations and Campaign Material, which are organized alphabetically by name group or candidate.
Detailed List of Contents
- Governance, id134665
  Scope and Contents
  The series is the largest of the collection and is comprised of materials related to the governance of ROADwomen including financial and membership records, by-laws and other material pertaining to the incorporation of the organization. The sub-series concerned with meetings consist of materials and clippings pertinent to the meeting in question but are not meeting minutes.
  - History and Incorporation, id134675
    - History, 1997; id134703 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Incorporation, 1997; id134704 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - By-Laws, 2001-2005; id134705 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Corporation Amendments, 2005; id134706 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Logo, 1997; id134707 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - ROADgoals, 2000; id134708 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Committees, id134676
    - Committees, 1997; id134710 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee, 1997-1999; id134711 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee, 2000; id134712 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee, 2004; id134713 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Newsletter Committee, 1997; id134714 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Membership, id134677
    - Membership List, 1997; id134716 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Membership Roster, 1997; id134717 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Membership Roster, 1997-1998; id134718 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Membership Roster, 1997-1998; id134719 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Membership Roster, 1998; id134720 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Membership Roster, 1999; id134721 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Membership Roster, 2000; id134722 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Membership Roster, 2000-2001; id134723 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Membership List, 2002; id134724 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Membership Roster, 2002; id134726 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Membership Materials, 2003; id134727 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Membership Roster, 2003; id134728 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Membership Materials, 2004; id134729 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Membership Roster, 2004; id134730 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Membership Forms, undated; id134731 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Non-member Sign-in Sheets, 1999-2003; id134732 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Financials, id134678
    - Internal Revenue Service, id134684
      - IRS, 1998-2004; id134735 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - IRS, 2003; id134736 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Invoices, id134685
      - Invoices, 1998; id134738 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Invoices, 1999; id134739 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Invoices, 2000; id134740 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Invoices, 2002; id134741 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Invoices, 2003; id134742 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Invoices, 2004; id134743 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Invoices, 2005; id134744 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Texas Ethics Commission, id134686
      - Appointment of Campaign Treasurer, id134688
        - Appointment of Campaign Treasurer, 1997-1998; id134746 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        - Appointment of Campaign Treasurer, 2003; id134747 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        - Appointment of Campaign Treasurer, 2005; id134748 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Reports, id134689
        - Report, 1997-1998; id134750 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        - Report, 1998; id134751 (Box 4, Folder 2)
        - Report, 1999-2000; id134752 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        - Report, 2001; id134753 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        - Report, August 2004; id134754 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        - Report, September 2004; id134755 (Box 4, Folder 6)
        - Report, October 2004; id134756 (Box 4, Folder 7)
        - Report, November 2004; id134757 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        - Report, December 2004; id134758 (Box 4, Folder 9)
        - Report, January 2005; id134759 (Box 4, Folder 10)
        - Report, February 2005; id134760 (Box 4, Folder 11)
        - Report, March 2005; id134761 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Various Materials, id134690
        - 30th Day Before Election, 1997-1998; id134763 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - 8th Day Before Election, 1997-1998; id134764 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - Kay Staley, 1999-2000; id134765 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - PAC Formation, 1998; id134766 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Various Financial Materials, id134687
      - Franchise Tax, 1994-2005; id134768 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Hansfam Three Trust, 2002; id134769 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Space Place Storage, 2001; id134770 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Meetings/ROADgathering, id134679
    - Meeting Location Options, 1994-2000; id134773 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Meeting, April 1997; id134774 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Meeting, May 1997; id134775 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Meeting, June 1997; id134776 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Meeting, July 1997; id134777 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Meeting, August 1997; id134778 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Meeting, September 1997; id134779 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Meeting, October 1997; id134780 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Meeting, November 1997; id134781 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Meeting, January 1998; id134782 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Meeting, February 1998; id134783 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Special Meeting-Precinct Convention Workshop, March 1998; id134784 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Meeting, March 1998; id134785 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Meeting, April 1998; id134786 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, May 1998; id134787 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, June 1998; id134788 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, July 1998; id134789 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, September 1998; id134790 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, October 1998; id134791 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, November 1998; id134792 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, January 1999; id134793 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, February 1999; id134794 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, March 1999; id134795 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, April 1999; id134796 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, May 1999; id134797 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Meeting, June 1999; id134798 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Meeting, July 1999; id134799 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Meeting, August 1999; id134800 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Meeting, October 1999; id134801 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Meeting, November 1999; id134802 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Meeting, January 2000; id134803 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Meeting, February 2000; id134804 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Meeting, March 2000; id134805 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Meeting, April 2000; id134806 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Meeting, May 2000; id134807 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Meeting, June 2000; id134808 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Meeting, July 2000; id134809 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Meeting, October 2000; id134810 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - ROADgathering, January 2001; id134812 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - ROADgathering, February 2001; id134813 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ROADgathering, March 2001; id134814 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ROADgathering, April 2001; id134815 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - ROADgathering, May 2001; id134816 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - ROADgathering, July 2001; id134817 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - ROADgathering, September 2001; id134818 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - ROADgathering, October 2001; id134819 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - ROADgathering, November 2001; id134820 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - ROADgathering, January 2002; id134821 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - ROADgathering, February 2002; id134822 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - ROADgathering, March 2002; id134823 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - ROADgathering, May 2002; id134824 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - ROADgathering, June 2002; id134825 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - ROADgathering, July 2002; id134826 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - ROADgathering, August 2002; id134827 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - ROADgathering, September 2002; id134828 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - ROADgathering, October 2002; id134829 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - ROADgathering, November 2002; id134830 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - ROADgathering, January 2003; id134831 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - ROADgathering, February 2003; id134832 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - ROADgathering, March 2003; id134833 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - ROADgathering, April 2003; id134834 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - ROADgathering, May 2003; id134835 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - ROADgathering, June 2003; id134836 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - ROADgathering, July 2003; id134837 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - ROADgathering, August 2003; id134838 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - ROADgathering, September 2003; id134839 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - ROADgathering, October 2003; id134840 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - ROADgathering, January 2004; id134841 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - ROADgathering, February 2004; id134842 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - ROADgathering, March 2004; id134843 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - ROADgathering, April 2004; id134844 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - ROADgathering, May 2004; id134845 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Texas Democratic Party Convention, June 2004; id134846 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Democratic National Convention-Boston, July 2004; id134847 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - ROADgathering, September 2004; id134848 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - ROADgathering, October 2004; id134849 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - ROADgathering, November 2004; id134850 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - ROADgathering, January 2005; id134851 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - ROADgathering, February 2005; id134852 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - ROADgathering Front Desk, undated; id134853 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Website, id134680
    - Website, 1997; id134855 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Website, 1998; id134856 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Website, 1998; id134857 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, id134681
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998; id134859 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1998-2004; id134860 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Email and Various Correspondence, 1997-1998; id134861 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Email, 1999-2000; id134862 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Email, 2005; id134863 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Email Addresses, 1999; id134864 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations, id134682
    - Potential Advertising Venues, 1998; id134866 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Press Releases: Affirmative Action, 1997; id134867 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Promotions, undated; id134868 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Public Relations, 1997-1999; id134869 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - ROADbooth at State Convention, 1998; id134870 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - ROADbooth at Women United, 1999; id134871 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Polls and Surveys, id134683
    - ROADpoll, 1998; id134873 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - ROADpoll, March 2002; id134874 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - ROADpoll, April 2003; id134875 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - ROADpoll Primary, 2004; id134876 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - ROADwomen Rating, 1998; id134877 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Survey Responses, April 2005; id134878 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- ROADwomen Register, id134666
  This series consists of the organization’s newsletter. Each folder contains the newsletter that corresponds to the date and most contain drafts of the newsletter as well as materials included in the publication. Register primarily focuses on the activities of ROADwomen but also discusses issues pertinent to the organization.
  - Register, June 1997; id134883 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Register, July 1997; id134884 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Register, August 1997; id134885 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Register, September 1997; id134886 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Register, October 1997; id134887 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Register, November 1997; id134888 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Register, December 1997; id134889 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Various Material for Register, 1997; id134890 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Special Edition Election ’98, 1998; id134891 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Register, January 1998; id134892 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Register, February 1998; id134893 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Register, March 1998; id134894 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Register, April 1998; id134895 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Register, May 1998; id134896 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Register, June 1998; id134897 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Register, July 1998; id134898 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Register, August 1998; id134899 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Register, September 1998; id134900 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Register, October 1998; id134901 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Register, November 1998; id134902 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Register, December 1998; id134903 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Register, January 1999; id134904 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Register, February 1999; id134905 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Register, March 1999; id134906 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Register, April 1999; id134907 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Register, May 1999; id134908 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Register, June 1999; id134909 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Register, July 1999; id134910 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Register, August 1999; id134911 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Register, September 1999; id134912 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Register, October 1999; id134913 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Register, November 1999; id134914 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Register, December 1999; id134915 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Register, 2000; id134916 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Register, 2000; id134917 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Register, 2000; id134918 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Register, 2000; id134919 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Register, 2000; id134920 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Register, 2000; id134921 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Register, 2000; id134922 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Register, 2000; id134923 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Register, 2000; id134924 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Register, 2000; id134925 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Register, 2000; id134926 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Register, 2000; id134927 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Register, 2000; id134928 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Register, 2000; id134929 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Register, 2000; id134930 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Register, 2000; id134931 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Register, 2000; id134932 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Register, 2000; id134933 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Register, 2000; id134934 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Register, 2000; id134935 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Register, 2000; id134936 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Register, 2000; id134937 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Register, 2000; id134938 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Register, 2000; id134939 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Register, 2000; id134940 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Register, 2000; id134941 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Register, 2000; id134942 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Register, 2000; id134943 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Register, 2000; id134944 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Register, September 2002; id134950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Register, October 2002; id134951 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Register, November 2002; id134952 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Register, January 2003; id134953 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Register, February 2003; id134954 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Register, March 2003; id134955 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Register, April 2003; id134956 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Register, May 2003; id134957 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Register, June 2003; id134958 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Register, July 2003; id134959 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Register, August 2003; id134960 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Register, September 2003; id134961 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Register, October 2003; id134962 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Register, December 2003; id134963 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Register, January 2004; id134964 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Register, February 2004; id134965 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Register, March 2004; id134966 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Register, April 2004; id134967 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Register, May 2004; id134968 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Register, June 2004; id134969 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Register, July 2004; id134970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Register, August 2004; id134971 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Register, October 2004; id134972 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Register, January 2005; id134973 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Register, February 2005; id134974 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Register, March 2005; id134975 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Register, April 2005; id134976 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Register, June-August, October-November 2005; id134977 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Register, February-May 2006; id134978 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Register, June/July-November 2006; id134979 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Register, July 2008; id134980 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Events and Programs, id134667
  This series contains materials on events hosted by ROADwomen as well as programs in which the organization participated. Arianna Live! is an event that featured Arianna Huffington, president and editor-in-chief of the Huffington Post. The Fork in the Road Benefits were held by ROADwomen as fundraisers for the organization and as a means to periodically give money to various Democratic clubs, organizations, and candidates, as well as to further the general mission of the group.
  - Arianna Live!, id134691
    - Ads/Promos, 2004; id134982 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Books, 2004; id134983 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Budget, 2004; id134984 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Candidates, 2004; id134985 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Contracts/ Insurance, 2004; id134986 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Hobby Center, 2004-2006; id134987 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Installations/ Flyers, 2004; id134988 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Invitees, 2004; id134989 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Postcard Mailer, 2004; id134990 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Program, 2004; id134991 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Program/Script/Timeline, 2004; id134992 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Royce Clayton, Inc., 2004; id134993 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Seating Charts/ Ticket Sales, 2004; id134994 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Sponsors, 2004; id134995 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - VIPs, 2004; id134996 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Fork in the Road Benefits, id134692
    - Fork I, id134696
      - Correspondence, 1998; id134998 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      - Financials, 1998; id134999 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      - Forrest J. “Frosty” Troy, 1998; id135000 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - Invitations and Programs, 1998; id135001 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Membership Lists and Information, 1998; id135002 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Messages, 1998; id135003 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      - Printed Materials, 1998; id135004 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      - Tables and Seating, 1998; id135005 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Fork II, id134697
      - Accounting, 1999; id135007 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Awards and Gifts, 1999; id135008 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Committee, 1999; id135009 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - General, 1999; id135010 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Financials, 1999; id135011 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Invitees, 1999; id135012 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Invitation, 1999; id135013 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Public Relations, 1999; id135014 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Register Report and Phones, 1999; id135015 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - ROADscholars, 1999; id135016 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Sponsor Letter, 1999; id135017 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Schedule Program, 1999; id135018 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Speakers, 1999; id135019 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Stationery, 1999; id135020 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Table Assignments, 1999; id135021 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Thank Yous and Post Event, 1999; id135022 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Tony’s Ballroom, 1999; id135023 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Fork III, id134698
      - Booker/Hancock Public Relations, 2000; id135025 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Congressional Recognition, 2000; id135026 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2001; id135027 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Favors/Door Prizes, 2000; id135028 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Financials, 2000; id135029 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Financials, 2000; id135030 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - General, 2000; id135031 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Honorees/Awards, 2000; id135032 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Invitations, 2000; id135033 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Membership Information, 2000; id135034 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Photographs, 2000; id135035 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Post-Event, 2000; id135036 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Sponsor Letter, 2000; id135037 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Strategic Planning Session, 2000; id135038 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Table Settings, 2000; id135039 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Table Settings, 2000; id135040 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Various Printed Materials, 2000; id135041 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Video Al Gore/Program, 2000; id135042 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Volunteers, 2000; id135043 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Westin Oaks, 2000; id135044 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Various Fork Materials, 2005-2006; id135045 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Mayoral Forum, id134693
    - Mailing Lists, 1997; id135047 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Various Materials, 1997; id135048 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Precinct Initiative, id134694
    - Precinct Initiative, 1998; id135050 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Precinct Initiative, 2000; id135051 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Various Events and Programs, id134695
    - 97 TALK Democratic Perspective, 1998; id135053 (Box 12, Folder 5)